{
    "subject": "resource/Julie_Andrews",
    "predicate": "ontology/spouse",
    "object": "resource/Blake_Edwards",
    "human_readable": "Julie Andrews was married to Blake Edwards.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9885140061378479,
            "question": "Was Blake Edwards married to Julie Andrews?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.924825131893158,
            "question": "How long were Julie Andrews and Blake Edwards married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9119648933410645,
            "question": "Who was Julie Andrews married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8493902087211609,
            "question": "Who are Julie Andrews and Blake Edwards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5920173525810242,
            "question": "What is the name of Julie Andrews' husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5557600855827332,
            "question": "Did Blake Edwards and Julie Andrews work together on any projects?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28590619564056396,
            "question": "What is Julie Andrews best known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2721635699272156,
            "question": "What are some of the famous works associated with Blake Edwards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16225527226924896,
            "question": "Were there any notable events in their marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06108377128839493,
            "question": "What is known about their relationship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Julie Andrews was married to Blake Edwards.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7168_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable events in their marriage?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7168_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the famous works associated with Blake Edwards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7168_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Julie Andrews best known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7168_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7168_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7168_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7168_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7168_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7168_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7168_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7168_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7168_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7168_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7168_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Julie Andrews was married to Blake Edwards, supporting the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}